A Guide to the Governor L. Douglas Wilder Transition Office, 1988-1990
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Governor L. Douglas Wilder Transition Office, 1988-1990 (bulk 1989-1990)
The Library of Virginia
35539
1.4 cu. ft.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from Governor L. Douglas Wilder on 31 October 1996.
Biographical Information
Governor-Elect L. Douglass Wilder began assembling his transition team shortly after winning election on 7 November 1989, naming Mark Warner Director of the Transition Office, with Paul Goldman as Deputy Director. Laura Dillard, Press Secretary and Richard Taylor, Policy Director during Wilder's Gubernatorial campaign remand in those positons during the transition.
Scope and Content
Records, 1988-1990 (bulk 1989-1990) of the Transition Office of Governor L. Douglas Wilder. The collection is housed in 4 boxes and includes correspondence, notebooks, reports, summaries, and other documents. The bulk of the collection consists of Agency Position Summaries, which contain information about Agencies, Agency Heads and their budgets and Transition notebooks and papers detailing the structure of the executive branch along with important dates and information needed by the incoming administration.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged alphabetically by folder title.
Contents List
- Agency Position Summary, 1989-1990. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Agency Position Summary, 1989-1990. (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Agency Position Summary, 1989-1990. (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Agency Position Summary, 1989-1990. (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Agency Position Summary, 1989-1990. (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Agency Position Summary, 1989-1990. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Agency Position Summary, 1989-1990. (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Agency Position Summary, 1989-1990. (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Agency Position Summary, 1989-1990. (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Appointments, 1989-1990. (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Baliles, Gov. Gerald L.--Speech, 1989. (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Campaign Management, 1989. (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Congratulations, 1989. (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Correspondence--Delegates, 1989. (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Correspondence--General, 1988-1989. (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Correspondence--General, 1989. (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Invitations, 1989. (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Jamestown-Yorktown, 1989. (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Secretary of Administration, 1989. (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Southern Political Report, 1989. (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Telegrams, 1989. (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Transition Notebook vol. 1, 1989. (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Transition Notebook vol. 1, 1989. (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Transition Notebook vol. 2, 1989. (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Transition Notebook vol. 2, 1989. (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Transition Papers for Governor-Elect, 1989-1990. (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Transition Papers for Governor-Elect, 1989-1990. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Transition Report vol. 2, 1989. (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1989. (Box 4, Folder 4)